<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Classes on All Articles</title>
    <link>https://akl5000.github.io/series/classes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Classes on All Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://akl5000.github.io/series/classes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assassin</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/assassin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/assassin/</guid>
      <description>Assassin Assassins rely on skill, stealth, and their foes’ vulnerabilities to get the upper hand in any situation. They have a knack for finding the solution to just about any problem, demonstrating a resourcefulness and versatility that is the cornerstone of any successful adventuring party.
Skill and Precision Assassins devote as much effort to mastering the use of a variety of skills as they do to perfecting their combat abilities, giving them a broad expertise that few other characters can match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beggar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/beggar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/beggar/</guid>
      <description>Beggar From the naive eye, beggars look like a plague that coat the cities across the continent. But others, those who understand the wisdom hidden behind the beggars few words, understand the true worth of those people.
Wisdom from the Land Beggars are the brain of the continent. A band of brothers making up the poorest people of the continent, but with the skills to rival the major guilds. Alone, a beggar can become a formidable foe, but together, their combined wisdom and experiences can make armies crumble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blademaster</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/blademaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/blademaster/</guid>
      <description>Blademaster The Blademaster weighs down his limbs for the promise of strength in the future. Swinging their blades, mimicking a whirlwind. An unstoppable force that dictates the flow of the battle from the front lines. While swordsmen value fancy essence sword skills and frivolous footwork, the Blademaster opts for raw strength and speed.
Constant training To maintain the raw strength they require for their skills. Blademasters choose to always carry weight on themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brutalist</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/brutalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/brutalist/</guid>
      <description>Brutalist While other fighting styles choose to imbue their weaponry and movements with essence. Brutalists take a more intrusive approach. By brutally infusing their bodies with essence, an unarmed fighting style becomes most effective. Whether or not a brutalist uses this power to bring health or destruction is up to them.
Imbued palms The brutalist fighting style utilizes the lightweight capabilities of martial arts. With the essence flowing through their bodies, their palms become as deadly as a sword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Militant</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/militant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/militant/</guid>
      <description>Militant Over the course of history, the kings and generals of the world have learned the that the most powerful weapon on the battlefield is a spear. Its range and elusiveness counter any novice swordsman. The spearmen of the continent are referred to as Militants because of this fact. The best Militants are trained into generals, learning the spear arts of the kingdoms they serve.
Discipline and service Militants are hearty, loyal, soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranger</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/ranger/</guid>
      <description>Ranger Far from the bustle of cities and towns, past the most distant farms close to the terrors of the wild, amid the dense-packed trees of trackless forests and across wide and empty plains, rangers keep their unending watch. While the bow and arrow are considered lowly compared to the fierce close quartered arts of the sword or spear, a true master of the bow can make any person, no matter the strength, feel real despair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soundsmith</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/soundsmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/soundsmith/</guid>
      <description>Soundsmith Ascetics and musicians roam the continent, but few infuse their music with essence. Those who do inspire and delight people wherever they may travel. Among those people, even fewer are prepared to use their talent for battle. Those people, those who will inspire their comrades while having the will to destroy their foes, are called Soundsmiths.
Battle Maestro Soundsmiths are few and far between, but no modern battle has ever been won without them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swordsman</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/swordsman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/swordsman/</guid>
      <description>Swordsman Still the most dominant style of fighting, Swordsmen continue the long history and lineage of the best warriors on the continent. Fighting alongside the power of the scales, swordsmen triumph with swift and decisive slashes, pushing the essence in their bodies to the limit, and creating art with their movements.
Tradition The most practiced and distinguished sword techniques hail from the great sword sects across the continent. These techniques employ basic sword maneuvers imbued with the power of the scales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
