<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on All Articles</title>
    <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on All Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://akl5000.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assassin</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/assassin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/assassin/</guid>
      <description>Assassin Assassins rely on skill, stealth, and their foes’ vulnerabilities to get the upper hand in any situation. They have a knack for finding the solution to just about any problem, demonstrating a resourcefulness and versatility that is the cornerstone of any successful adventuring party.
Skill and Precision Assassins devote as much effort to mastering the use of a variety of skills as they do to perfecting their combat abilities, giving them a broad expertise that few other characters can match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azzar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/azzar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/azzar/</guid>
      <description>Azzar The Azzar are mystical people of otherworldly grace, living in the world but not entirely part of it. They know much about the physical realm around them, but also of the substances in between. They walk proudly through a world that greets them with fearful incomprehension, and between worlds that are closer together than we could know. The Azzar are not just the protectors of the space scale, they were born from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beggar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/beggar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/beggar/</guid>
      <description>Beggar From the naive eye, beggars look like a plague that coat the cities across the continent. But others, those who understand the wisdom hidden behind the beggars few words, understand the true worth of those people.
Wisdom from the Land Beggars are the brain of the continent. A band of brothers making up the poorest people of the continent, but with the skills to rival the major guilds. Alone, a beggar can become a formidable foe, but together, their combined wisdom and experiences can make armies crumble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blademaster</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/blademaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/blademaster/</guid>
      <description>Blademaster The Blademaster weighs down his limbs for the promise of strength in the future. Swinging their blades, mimicking a whirlwind. An unstoppable force that dictates the flow of the battle from the front lines. While swordsmen value fancy essence sword skills and frivolous footwork, the Blademaster opts for raw strength and speed.
Constant training To maintain the raw strength they require for their skills. Blademasters choose to always carry weight on themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood-Touched</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/blood-touched/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/blood-touched/</guid>
      <description>Blood-Touched To be greeted with stares and whispers, to suffer violence and insult on the street, to see mistrust and fear in every eye: this is the lot of the Blood-Touched. And to twist the knife, Blood-Touched know that this is because a pact struck generations ago infused the essence of Maglore—The ancient blood god—into their bloodline. Their appearance and nature are not their fault but the result of an ancient sin, for which they and their children and their children’s children will always be held prisoner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brutalist</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/brutalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/brutalist/</guid>
      <description>Brutalist While other fighting styles choose to imbue their weaponry and movements with essence. Brutalists take a more intrusive approach. By brutally infusing their bodies with essence, an unarmed fighting style becomes most effective. Whether or not a brutalist uses this power to bring health or destruction is up to them.
Imbued palms The brutalist fighting style utilizes the lightweight capabilities of martial arts. With the essence flowing through their bodies, their palms become as deadly as a sword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character Creation Guide</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/character-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/character-creation/</guid>
      <description>Character Creation Guide People like to make characters in very different ways. Some enjoy creating an elaborate backstory, and choose the class and race after, while others have a class in mind and make the afterward. However, you may do it, here is a list of things that are required for a completed character.
Class Race Background Backstory Because of the interconnectedness between the classes, races, and world in this homebrew, I would recommend choosing a class first, followed by race, then background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/control-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/control-magic/</guid>
      <description>Control Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/dark-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/dark-magic/</guid>
      <description>Dark Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/earth-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/earth-magic/</guid>
      <description>Earth Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/fire-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/fire-magic/</guid>
      <description>Fire Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of the world</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/timeline/</guid>
      <description>History of Eribar The history of the Eribar can be divided up into 3 periods.
Ancient era (AE) Chaos State Post-Chaos (PC) Ancient era The ancient era can be best described in sub-eras. As much of the history of this time was lost in the Chaos State, only large-scale events were remembered. For this reason, only rough estimates of dates are known.
Pre-Discovery During this time, settlements were few and far between, with most creatures hunting and creating small scale farms to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/human/</guid>
      <description>Human In the reckonings of most worlds, Humans are the foundation of the global stage. Proud, family driven, and short-lived in comparison to Spirit Beasts and Azzars. Perhaps it is because of their shorter lives that they strive to achieve as much as they can in the years they are given. Or maybe they feel they have something to protect from the foreign races, and that’s why they build their mighty empires on the foundation of conquest and trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to DND Mechanics</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/intro-mechanics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/intro-mechanics/</guid>
      <description>Introductions to the Mechanics of DND Playing DND consists of 2 general gameplay modes, Adventuring and Combat. All sessions consist of one or more of these modes. In this section, I will try to summarize the two modes to hopefully give some clarity about what situations might arise in a typical session. After that, I will try to cover the dice and chance aspect of the game, along with an explanation of how your ability scores and skills come into play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the World of Eribar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/world-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/world-intro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the world of Eribar! You will soon play in this world, so I can’t give out all its secrets, but I can give you worldly knowledge that almost everyone living on the continent knows.
Foreign objects The Continent of Eribar is home to 9 mythical objects called scales. Each scale is roughly the size of a 2-story house. The scales are hard as diamonds, slightly reflective, and warm to the touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/metal-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/metal-magic/</guid>
      <description>Metal Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Militant</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/militant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/militant/</guid>
      <description>Militant Over the course of history, the kings and generals of the world have learned the that the most powerful weapon on the battlefield is a spear. Its range and elusiveness counter any novice swordsman. The spearmen of the continent are referred to as Militants because of this fact. The best Militants are trained into generals, learning the spear arts of the kingdoms they serve.
Discipline and service Militants are hearty, loyal, soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rage Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/rage-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/rage-magic/</guid>
      <description>Rage Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranger</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/ranger/</guid>
      <description>Ranger Far from the bustle of cities and towns, past the most distant farms close to the terrors of the wild, amid the dense-packed trees of trackless forests and across wide and empty plains, rangers keep their unending watch. While the bow and arrow are considered lowly compared to the fierce close quartered arts of the sword or spear, a true master of the bow can make any person, no matter the strength, feel real despair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for Weapons and Items</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/items-weapons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/items-weapons/</guid>
      <description>Resources for Weapons and Items DND has a surprisingly low number of weapons and a surprisingly large number of miscellaneous items.
Weapons Here is a full List of Weapons that we will be using in the game. Additional weapons are listed below.
Custom Weapons
Name Cost Damage Weight Properties Machete 10 gp 1d4 Slashing 3 lbs Finesse, Light Cutlas 15 gp 1d6 Slashing 3 lbs Light Armor and Shields Every class can choose between different types of armor to set their AC, see all the different types below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soundsmith</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/soundsmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/soundsmith/</guid>
      <description>Soundsmith Ascetics and musicians roam the continent, but few infuse their music with essence. Those who do inspire and delight people wherever they may travel. Among those people, even fewer are prepared to use their talent for battle. Those people, those who will inspire their comrades while having the will to destroy their foes, are called Soundsmiths.
Battle Maestro Soundsmiths are few and far between, but no modern battle has ever been won without them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/space-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/space-magic/</guid>
      <description>Space Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Beast</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/spiritbeast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/races/spiritbeast/</guid>
      <description>Spirit Beast The great Spirit Beasts of old once ruled the continent. Mystical dragons, serpents, fish, and even birds lived peacefully in the wilderness as they pleased. When conflict arose between the spirits of old and the conquering Humans, the most powerful Spirit Beasts took up arms to defeat the invaders. The two races met on the battlefield, with the elder spirit beasts arriving in humanoid form. The battle ended in stalemate, with both sides gaining a respect for each other, man to beast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swordsman</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/swordsman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/classes/swordsman/</guid>
      <description>Swordsman Still the most dominant style of fighting, Swordsmen continue the long history and lineage of the best warriors on the continent. Fighting alongside the power of the scales, swordsmen triumph with swift and decisive slashes, pushing the essence in their bodies to the limit, and creating art with their movements.
Tradition The most practiced and distinguished sword techniques hail from the great sword sects across the continent. These techniques employ basic sword maneuvers imbued with the power of the scales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Major Cities of Eribar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/major-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/major-cities/</guid>
      <description>The Major Cities of Eribar After the Chaos State, 9 major cities sprung from the ashes to protect the scale&amp;rsquo;s power from the world. Each city is unique and plays its own role in the current age.
Zara (Water) Stationed on the reef of the continent’s largest lake, Zara is a city of wealth and intellectuals. Peaked white spires can be seen rising up through the metropolis. The city is known not just for its immense wealth brought by the large costal trade networks spanning across land and sea, but also its large industrial hub, market districts, and large parties for the elite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/water-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/water-magic/</guid>
      <description>Water Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my Homebrew!</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/guides/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the wiki of my Homebrew! This homebrew introduces 8 classes, 4 races, a custom magic system, and a custom world named Eribar. Each of these Aspects can be found by navigating the tabs at the top. You can return back to this page under the Guides category
Suggested path of discovery Introduction to the world of Eribar (Optional – World Map, The Major Cities of Eribar, History of the World) If you know nothing about DND or need a refresher: Introduction to DND Mechanics Resources for Weapons and Items Character Creation Guide Browse the Classes Browse the Races Reference Magic type if class uses magic By this point you should be familiar with the world, classes, races, and have some idea about your backstory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/wood-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/wood-magic/</guid>
      <description>Wood Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Map</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/map/</guid>
      <description>World Map Race Map Region Borders </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
