<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World on All Articles</title>
    <link>https://akl5000.github.io/series/world.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in World on All Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://akl5000.github.io/series/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>History of the world</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/timeline.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/timeline.html</guid>
      <description>History of Eribar The history of the Eribar can be divided up into 3 periods.
Ancient era (AE) Chaos State Post-Chaos (PC) Ancient era The ancient era can be best described in sub-eras. As much of the history of this time was lost in the Chaos State, only large-scale events were remembered. For this reason, only rough estimates of dates are known.
Pre-Discovery During this time, settlements were few and far between, with most creatures hunting and creating small scale farms to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the World of Eribar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/world-intro.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/world-intro.html</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the world of Eribar! You will soon play in this world, so I can’t give out all its secrets, but I can give you worldly knowledge that almost everyone living on the continent knows.
Foreign objects The Continent of Eribar is home to 9 mythical objects called scales. Each scale is roughly the size of a 2-story house. The scales are hard as diamonds, slightly reflective, and warm to the touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Major Cities of Eribar</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/major-cities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/major-cities.html</guid>
      <description>The Major Cities of Eribar After the Chaos State, 9 major cities sprung from the ashes to protect the scale&amp;rsquo;s power from the world. Each city is unique and plays its own role in the current age.
Zara (Water) Stationed on the reef of the continent’s largest lake, Zara is a city of wealth and intellectuals. Peaked white spires can be seen rising up through the metropolis. The city is known not just for its immense wealth brought by the large costal trade networks spanning across land and sea, but also its large industrial hub, market districts, and large parties for the elite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Map</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/map.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/world/map.html</guid>
      <description>World Map Race Map Region Borders </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
