<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on All Articles</title>
    <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on All Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Control Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/control-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/control-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Control Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/dark-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/dark-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Dark Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/earth-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/earth-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Earth Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/fire-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/fire-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Fire Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/metal-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/metal-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Metal Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rage Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/rage-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/rage-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Rage Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/space-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/space-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Space Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/water-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/water-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Water Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood Magic</title>
      <link>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/wood-magic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akl5000.github.io/post/magic/wood-magic.html</guid>
      <description>Wood Magic Rules of spells. These spells are taken 1 for 1 from DND. A link to the DND spell will be included. The At higher levels mechanic is ignored, the Components mechanic is ignored, and the Level mechanic is ignored. The essence cost will always be listed. Cantrips are listed first, followed by all the other spells.
Cantrips are simple spells that you may use with only a little understanding of essence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
